medstore.biz 2012-03-12

# MedStore: prescription online pharmacy privacy policy

**Information We  Collect**  
We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect on our Web sites to provide you with a superior shopping experience and to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions.

**Your Account**  
When you place an order, we will ask you to set up “your account” which includes your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date, as well as certain other information when you order prescriptions. Using your account information, we will send you communications that we believe are relevant to you, including prescription refill and renewal reminders, newsletters and emails. If you prefer not to receive optional emails or other communications from us, you may adjust your account to prevent such communications by send us an email.

**Customer Reviews**  
We are pleased to hear from our customers and welcome your comments regarding our products. Customer Reviews allow other customers to see what you think about a product. We allow you the option of sharing your review anonymously by selecting “Anonymous” when submitting your review.

**Your Prescription Information**  
To fill your prescription drug order, we collect the following additional information: your date of birth, gender, drug allergies, medical conditions, illnesses, and current medications. If you plan to use insurance and you can’t find the member or group number, we ask that you provide your Social Security Number. Your Social Security Number is only used for purposes of seeking reimbursement from insurance companies.

**Information Automatically Collected**  
We automatically receive and collect certain types of information whenever you visit our Web stores. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies” and obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Web sites. This information includes the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, your browser software and operating system, your web server, the date and time you access our site, session information (such as download errors and page response times), information about your viewing, search and purchase history and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through, and from our Web sites. We use this information to monitor the usage and performance of our site, to enhance our customers’ search and shopping experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.

**Information From Third Parties**  
If we receive updated account information from third parties, we may revise your account for you so that we can efficiently process your orders, deliver your packages or otherwise communicate with you. For example, we may receive customer information from our shippers or from third parties with which we operate co-branded businesses. In addition, we may acquire customer names, email addresses and mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties.

**Other Information You Provide**  
We collect additional information that you choose to give us. For example, you provide information to us when you complete surveys or contest entry forms, add items to cart (if cart is available), sign up for special discounts or coupons, communicate with us by email, phone or otherwise, provide product reviews, or provide alternative delivery addresses.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**  
We protect all of your information against unauthorized access or release. We share your personal and prescription information with third parties as follows:

  * Brand Manufacturers — We may develop programs with some of our brand manufacturers through which you may be offered special discounts or coupons on products in exchange for providing your email address or completing a survey about the manufacturer’s products. When you are offered such discounts or coupons in exchange for providing information (for example, giving your email address or completing a survey), you will be notified that if you choose to participate, your name, email address and responses will be shared with the brand manufacturer. No other information will be shared.
  * Agents — We may enter into agreements with other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include sending promotional emails on our behalf to such companies’ customers; serving advertisements on our behalf, analyzing data; providing marketing assistance; processing credit card or debit card payments; and fulfilling and delivering orders. These companies and individuals have access to only to information necessary to perform their functions. They are not allowed to use the information for any other purpose and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information. We may share non-personal, summary, or aggregate customer data with partners and other third parties.
  * Business Transfers — We may buy or sell stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information is usually treated as one of the transferred business assets. Should our company or substantially all of either of their assets be sold, customer information will be one of the transferred business assets. In that event, we will post a notification on this page or send you an email so that you are always aware of how your information is being used.
  * Compliance with Law; Protection of Rights, Property or Safety — We will disclose account and other personal information when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other policies or user agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our business, our customers, or others.
  * As You Direct — If you direct, we will release prescription or other customer information to your authorized representative, the prescribing or other authorized practitioner caring for you, or such other person as you may direct. At the direction of the patient and to the extent specifically authorized by law, we will release such information to other persons, including insurance plans. For example, at your request we will automatically forward your prescription information to your insurance plan so that our company can directly handle reimbursement of your prescription purchase on your behalf.

From time to time, we may partner with certain companies who, in conjunction with their membership programs or rewards programs, require that we disclose purchasing information about their members who visit our Web store (for example, to earn points for purchases made on our site through links from the partner site). We will disclose only the information required to make these programs work for you and support your membership in them. In addition, we disclose this information to such companies only if you have consented first, including consent implied by your agreement to the membership or participation rules. If you do not want us to disclose that information to the strategic partner, then you must contact the partner directly. Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**Security**  
When you place an order online or use our site, your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet, We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database that is away from our Web site database so it isn’t connected to the Internet, to keep it safe from hackers.

**Cookies**  
To personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer and to retrieve certain information previously provided by you to us, so that you do not need to re-enter this information every time you shop at the site. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular web site or advertisement). Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can be accessed only when you enter your name and password. If you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject our cookies, you will not be able to make purchases from our Web stores or take advantage of many of our features.

**Unsolicited Email (SPAM)**  
Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes “harvest” your email address directly from your computer or another person’s address book or even obtain your email address through programs that automatically search web pages and email traffic for email addresses.

**Children**  
We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children’s products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Linked Web Sites**  
Our Web stores may contain links to and from other sites operated and maintained by separate companies. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites (including the Web sites of participants in our associate program) and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. The privacy policies of these sites may differ from our policy, so you should always review the privacy statement of each linked Web site you visit.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site (including through our customer service line), you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page or send you an email so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change.

**Your Comments**  
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to drop us a message by clicking here.
